I'm still a fan even though it's salty.
Hate to see you with some other, but know you happy.
Hate to see you happy if I'm not the one driving.
I'm so mature.
I got me a therapist to tell me there's other men I ain't doing.
One night and I just want you.
If I can't have you, no one should have mine.
I might get my ex.
Not the best idea.
His new girlfriend snakes how I can hear.
I might get my ex.
I still love him though.
Rather be in jail than alone.
I get the sense that it's a long cause.
I get the sense that you might really love her.
The sex gon' be evidence.
The sex is evidence.
I tried to ration with you.
No more is the crime of passion.
But damn.
You was hard to reach.
You was at the farmer's market with your perfect peach.
Now I'm in the basement.
Planting on my beige.
And now you laying face down.
Got me saying all about a piece.
I'm so mature.
I got me a therapist to tell me there's other men I ain't doing.
One night and I just want you.
If I can't have you, no one will.
I might get my ex.
Not the best idea.
His new girlfriend's next.
How'd I get here?
I might kill my ex.
I still love him though.
Rather be in jail than alone.
I did it all for love.
I did it all on no drugs.
I did all of this sober.
I did it all for us all.
I did it all for love.
I did it all on no drugs.
I did it all for us all.
I just killed my ex.
Not the best idea.
Killed his girlfriend next.
How'd I get here?
I just killed my ex.
I still love him though.
Rather be in jail than alone.
I did it all for love.
I did it all for us all.